

PERSONAL INFORMATION

I have a year's experience in studying and developing non-commerical projects in JavaScript and its React/Redux libraries. I'm also briefly acquainted with jQuery.

My main aim is to become a highly qualified specialist in the field of commercial projects development.

REWARDS AND CERTIFICATES

- First place in the "game design" nomination at the *Ludum Dare* gaming hackathon
- *Udemy* certificate at the end of the paid HTML and CSS course
- *Udemy* certificate at the end of the paid JavaScript and React/Redux libraries course
- *Udemy* certificate at the end of a paid course of advanced study of JavaScript and the React library
- Imaguru certificate of successful completion of the program of creation of one's own business

CONTACTS

Phone: +375291919565 Email: shpoisnik@gmail.com

Telegram: @shponik

Portfolio: https://pensive-lumiere-

78d935.netlify.app/

SOCIAL MEDIA





NIKITA SHALIMO

Frontend developer (Junior)

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Consulting services for the preparation and performing of course projects on the subject "Computer network hardware"

December 2020 - January 2022

Volunteer at the European Games 2019 in the direction of communication

May 2019 - July 2019

Assistance and consultation for athletes from 50 countries of the world (in English).

EDUCATION

Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics

Bachelor Degree, the Faculty of Computer Systems and Networks, specialty of Computing machines, Systems and Networks" | 2017 -2021.

PERSONAL QUALITIES

Purposeful, conscientious, hard-working, friendly, responsible, sociable.

SKILLS

- HTML5/CSS3/SCSS
- JavaScript/React/Redux
- Webpack/Gulp
- Axios/REST API
- npm/yarn
- Git/GitHub
- Scrum Development
- Game Development (Unity3D)
- Experience in administration between Linux and Windows
- Experience in working with JavaFX framework
- Experience in working with SQL data bases

ENGLISH INTERMEDIATE

Intermediate level B1